Futon, clothes, shoes, toothbrush...
What else...?
Huh?!
Rin, don't disappear like that! You scared me!
Okay.
Daikichi, can you pick me a green one?
Come on, let's go.
It's dangerous not to hold hands.
For me?
ashita no koto wa wakannai
We don't know what'll happen tomorrow.
kore tte gisei to wa chigau
This feels different from a sacrifice.
nanika ga chigau
Something feels different.
batsu ge-mu ja nante omowanai
I'm not thinking of it as a punishment game.
de nande na no ka wa wakannai
I still don't know why.
chotto shakuzen to shinai kedo
Even though I don't quite feel satisfied with that,
kimi no sonzai ima daiji da nante mon ja nai
there's no question that you're important to me now.
owaranai koto nante kono yo no doko ni mo nai
There's nothing in this world that's endless.
naku no wa tsurain ja nai no
Isn't it painful having to cry?
ai no Sweet Drops, Sweet Drops
Love's sweet drops, sweet drops.
zutto yume mite itai ne
Don't you want to keep dreaming forever?
motto yasashiku shitai ne
Don't you want to be kinder?
kimi to iraretara Happy
As long as I'm with you, I'm happy.
onna no ko tte tsuyoi ne
Don't you think girls can be strong?
dakedo tokidoki yowai ne
Even though we can be weak sometimes.
bokura no negai wa Happy Happy Happy
Our wish is for happy, happy, happy.
sonna hibi mo Happy
Those days can also be happy.
Just wanna make you happy
Just wanna make you happy.
Who knew this many parents would bring their kids here?
I want that one!
This?
Yep!
Well, okay. This looks good.
What size are you?
I don't know.
Rin, turn around.
Like this?
Where should I compare the sizes?
I dunno!
Don't flap around!
What else do you need?
Pajamas, underwear, shirts, socks!
What about skirts? All you have are pants.
We're not allowed to wear skirts at the day-care center.
I see...
Day-care center?!
I forgot! Tomorrow is Monday!
Daikichi, I'm tired...
We're almost there. Just bear with it.
Okay...
I'm hungry...
We're almost home, so...
Okay...
Excuse me.
Hello, this is the Maeda family.
Yes, I am very sorry for your loss.
Yes, please hold on one moment.
Haruko-san, it's Daikichi-san.
Yes! Sorry about that!
Ah, Haruko. Sorry, I didn't ask for your cell number.
It's fine.
Say, how do you enroll in a day-care center?
Day-care?
What?! You really brought Rin-chan home with you?
Wait, are you sure that's okay?
For the time being.
For the time being?
Anyway, I have to go back to work tomorrow. What should I do?
You know, you can't just enroll her on such short notice.
Can't you do something about that?
Even if you ask me that...
For now, you could ask at the city hall.
But it's Sunday night.
What?
No, it's nothing.
Are you all right?
Not now, Reina! This is an important conversation.
Rin-chan!
They have a temporary emergency day-care.
Temporary emergency day-care...
Rin-chan!
What happened? Dai-chan?
Rin-chan, Rin-chan, Rin-chan, Rin-chan!
No, it's nothing.
I'll be done soon, hold on!
Reina's impatient!
Haruko-san, I'm turning off the miso soup.
Ah, sorry about that!
You seem busy, so I'll—
Rin-chan!!
There aren't many...
Suddenly, my commute has doubled.
I'm fine.
This one's nearby, but I can't get off work by 6.
Yeah. Yeah. Let's play again next time.
Bye bye.
See you, Reina-chan!
This one looks good, but the temporary day-care service is only for ten days.
Bath.
Wait a little longer.
Daikichi.
It's morning.
Okay, sorry...
Were you sleeping over here?
The futon is strangely warm.
Take this off!
Okay, okay.
You'll be going to day-care today.
Let's eat...
Let's eat!
Don't eat with your elbows on the table!
Right, sorry.
Listen, the day-care I'm taking you to now is only temporary.
Temporary?
It's just until I decide on a place for you to officially attend.
What's "officially" mean?
Doing things the proper way.
Well, not quite.
My hair is fine!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I-I'm fine.
There it is!
Let me down! Let me down!
What? What is it?
Are you embarrassed about the other kids seeing me carry you?
Daikichi.
Yeah...
Then, I'll leave her in your care.
Of course, have a nice day!
Don't make that face.
I won't be back until after dark, but I'll come as soon as I can.
It's a promise.
Pinky promise, swallow a thousand needles if I lie.
Damn it, cut my finger off.
That's not how it goes.
See you later. Wait for me, Rin.
Sorry, Rin.
I wasn't able to pay attention to your feelings.
Your mother's circumstances and Grandfather's death
aren't really things you'd care about.
There's only the lonely truth that you were left all alone.
Did you think I'd abandon you, as well?
I'm sorry for making you go through that again.
Want to read?
Kawachi-san, let's go to lunch.
Oh, I brought this. I'm getting a head start today.
Ah, I see. I'm off, then.
Beginning of the month and you're already working hard.
Not really.
You can pick a photo from this sample.
Okay.
Kawachi-san, you have a call on line four
about the meeting for the private viewing.
Okay!
Hello, this is Kawachi.
Bye bye!
Bye bye.
Let's keep going!
Yeah.
Kawachi...
Yes, pardon me.
You're late!
Sorry, sorry.
Get your jacket on.
Okay!
Rin-chan, don't break it, okay?
Okay.
Bye bye.
Yes.
Please wait one moment.
Kawachi-san, it's Miyata-san from Mitsutomo Trading.
Hand it over.
Hello, this is Kawachi. Thank you for doing business with us.
Hello, this is Kawachi...
Yes. I'm very sorry...
Yes, I should be able to leave the office shortly. I apologize.
This day-care... is too far!
Rin! Sorry I'm late.
Welcome back.
I'm so sorry.
Rin.
Are these potatoes? They look delicious!
It's a sauté!
Daikichi
A thousand needles...
swallowed!
Then, I'll leave this to you.
Kawachi-san, your signature!
I probably don't need to worry about it, but what will happen if I get a girlfriend?
Daikichi!
Get up!
Okay, sorry...
Kawachi. This was supposed to get shipped yesterday.
I'm terribly sorry...
That's unusual for you.
I'm sorry.
I've already apologized to them.
I'm sorry. I'll give them a call.
It's been a while, let's go out drinking.
Sorry, I can't today.
Then, how about tomorrow?
Tomorrow doesn't work, either...
Oh, I see. Must be nice, huh?
Here.
I'm fine.
Daikichi!
Hold on tight!
Daikichi! Keep running from the moon!
All right!
It never ends!
I wonder how long I can keep this up.
Here, these are Rin-chan's.
This is all we have, but her maternity book and important documents are in there.
Even if it's just for a short time, raising a child can be very difficult.
It really must be hardest on Rin.
Sorry. I'll just take a little look.
Her mouth is still the same.
Everyone seems to think you're some kind of villain.
But really, who's the bad one here... Masako-san?
nichiyou no hareta hirusagari
It's a sunny Sunday, early in the afternoon.
kyou wa doko e yukou?
Where should we go today?
kayoi nareta itsumo no michi ga
This path I've grown so used to taking
mabushiku kagayaite mieru
seems to be shining brightly,
terasu atatakai taiyou to
as long as the warm sun is shining
tonari ni kimi ga ireba
and you are here beside me.
mou High High High
I'm already high, high, high.
hashagidasu kimochi ni
I feel like frolicking about.
utae Life Life Life
Let's sing, life, life, life.
koe wa dokomademo
Our voices can go anywhere.
mou High High High
I'm already high, high, high.
maiagaru kaze ni nori
I'm riding on the rising wind.
utae Life Life Life
Let's sing, life, life, life.
koe mo tobihaneru
Even our voices will be bouncing.
What's up? Is something wrong?
I mean, you're sleeping over there...
D-did I... Me?!
It's sweat!
All right. It's sweat, okay.
Help me take off the sheets.
I'm telling you it's sweat!
Didn't I say it was sweat, too?!